starfall.com 2019-12-29

# Starfall Education Privacy Policy

Starfall Education Foundation strives to create a safe and playful environment for all children. Throughout our services — the many Starfall Apps for mobile devices, the Starfall website for children ([www.starfall.com](https://www.starfall.com/)), the Starfall Parent-Teacher Center™ ([teach.starfall.com](https://teach.starfall.com/)), and the Starfall Store™ ([store.starfall.com](https://store.starfall.com/)) — we adhere to a strict policy of respecting and protecting the privacy of our users.

**Starfall does not collect personal information from children, or track children's progress.** We do not require children to provide personal information to use and access our services. The Starfall websites and apps directed toward children are compliant with COPPA and FERPA.

www.kidsafeseal.com 

## Personal Information Collection and Use

We ask adult users to provide information about himself or herself when logging in to the member portion of Starfall or when completing a purchase in our store. This information is not shared with any third party or partner and is used only for the narrow purpose for which it was entered.

  * **Basic Membership Information** : When you become a member of Starfall, you must provide general personal information such as your name, email address, and a password. We may again ask for this information when you login or when you make changes to your account. This information is used solely for identification purposes and is not shared with third parties including other members.
  * **Payment Information** : When you make a purchase, whether it is for an online membership or a physical product, we require billing and shipping information. This sensitive information is handled with the utmost care. We send payment information to a secure and nationally recognized payment processor using strong industry standard encryption. Once a purchase has been made we do not store credit card numbers, nor do we have access to credit card numbers through our payment processor. In order to provide customer service, we retain the details of a purchase, such as the payment date, the billing address, and the shipping address.

## Technical Information Collection and Use

When you use Starfall on a computer or mobile device, we collect some basic technical information in order to customize your experience as well as improve our services.

  * **Cookies** : Like many websites, we rely on cookies (a small text file sent to your browser) to give us a better understanding of how many unique users we have and how they are using our site. We also use cookies to retain your preferences and remember the state of an activity such as an online shopping cart or service such as a membership login. We do not collect personal information through cookies. We do not share cookie data with third parties nor do we use a third party to place cookies or report on usage data.
  * **Access Logs** : When you use Starfall we often receive information about your IP address, browser, operating system, or mobile device. We keep these records so that we can analyze the 'big picture' of how our visitors use our site and to analyze any technical problems that could occur.

## Social Media & Advertising

Starfall does not place third party advertisements or links to advertisements on our websites or other services. We strongly believe that children should not be the targets of marketing efforts during their educational experience. Resources for grown-ups, specifically those found on the Starfall Parent-Teacher Center™ and the Starfall Store™, may contain links to social media services, but are kept separate from children's activities and safeguarded behind a parent gate.

## Disclosure of Information

Starfall may disclose user information we have retained if we believe it necessary to comply with a legal process, law enforcement investigation, or government request. We may also divulge collected information in response to fraud or technical security issues or in matters of public safety. Any such disclosure will be tailored to disclose only the specifically requested information to the requesting authority.

## Updates

We may make changes to our privacy policy from time to time. Please feel free to revisit this page for the most up-to-date version.
